const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'Do you like singing.??',
    answers: ['yes, I am', 'yes, I do', 'yes, I was', 'yes, I did', 'yes, I were', 'yes, I have', 'yes, I had', 'yes, I will', 'yes, I would', 'yes, I can'],
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'People use me to taste food. What am I.??',
    answers: ['feet', 'eyes', 'hair', 'hands', 'nose', 'ears', 'lips', 'tongue', 'face', 'stomach'],
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `
      Meli: "Hi Aji! How are you.??"
      Aji: "I am fine thank you. What about you.??"
      Meli: "...... thank you."
    `,
    answers: ['See you tommorow', 'Goodbye', "You're fine", 'Nice to meet you', 'The weather is nice', 'Great', "It's cloudy", "I'm here", 'I say', 'I am'],
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `
      Farhan: "Can we go holiday on Monday.??"
      Doni: "..... we have to go to school."
    `,
    answers: ["Yes, we can't", 'Yes, we can', 'Yes, we will', "Yes, we won't", 'Yes, we do', 'No, we can', "No, we can't", 'No, we will', "No, we won't", "No, we don't"],
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: '.... Everest is the highest place in the world!!!',
    answers: ['Pool', 'River', 'Sea', 'Place', 'Mount', 'Valley', 'Zoo', 'Waterfall', 'Lake', 'Tower'],
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'She .... a doll.',
    answers: ['have', 'was', 'were', 'has', 'is', 'can', 'take', 'bring', 'make', 'may'],
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `
      Ella: ".... borrow your eraser, please.??"
      Roni: "Sure, here you are."
    `,
    answers: ['Can you', 'Do I', 'Will I', 'Will you', 'Do you', 'I can', 'Am I', 'May I', 'May you', 'You can'],
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'The students will not go to .... on sunday.',
    answers: ['Library', 'Shop', 'Museum', 'School', 'Airport', 'Harbor', 'Holiday', 'Vacation', 'Cafe', 'Terminal'],
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'The color of the sky is ....',
    answers: ['Blue', 'Red', 'Yellow', 'Green', 'White', 'Black', 'Purple', 'Indigo', 'Violet', 'Grey'],
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'The color of the sun is ....',
    answers: ['Blue', 'Red', 'Yellow', 'Green', 'White', 'Black', 'Purple', 'Indigo', 'Violet', 'Grey'],
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'On a rainy day, the activity that is suitable for us is ....',
    answers: ['play football', 'play kite', 'take a walk', 'go to park', 'go jogging', 'play game indoor', 'dry clothes', 'climb a tree', 'make paper plane', 'plant tree'],
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'Fifteen days before Monday is ....',
    answers: ['Monday', 'Friday', 'Wednesday', 'Afternon', 'Evening', 'Saturday', 'Sunday', 'Morning', 'Thursday', 'Tuesday'],
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: `
      1. Hello, Santi.
      2. Hello, Mr. Hartono. Nice to meet you.
      3. His name is Hartono
      4. Nice to meet you, Atiqah.
      5. Hi, Atiqah.
      6. Atiqah, this is my father.
      Arrange the following sentences into good dialogue!!
    `,
    answers: ['5-1-6-2-3-4', '5-1-2-4-6-3', '5-1-6-4-2-3', '5-1-2-3-6-4', '5-1-3-2-6-4', '5-1-6-2-4-3', '5-1-4-3-6-2', '5-1-3-6-2-4', '5-1-6-3-2-4', '5-1-3-6-4-2'],
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: 'Yusuf is a philatelist. He is very fond of colecting ....',
    answers: ['envelopes', 'cashes', 'letters', 'coins', 'watches', 'papers', 'stamps', 'rings', 'pendulum', 'stones'],
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: `
      Ari meets Chandra and Sigit at the bus station.
      .... are going to Bandung in a couple of hours.
    `,
    answers: ['We', 'You', 'I', 'He', 'They', 'Our', 'It', 'Us', 'Them', 'She'],
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: 'Which sentence is the correct one.??',
    answers: [
      'The pen was give to me yesterday',
      'Tomorrow I went to school',
      'Lisa sing my favourite song',
      'This book should been at library yesterday',
      'I am gonna find my wallet soon',
      'We plays football at the yard',
      'He like banana',
      'They play hide and seek yesterday',
      'I at the school now',
      'I had been finished watching that movie tomorrow afternoon',
    ],
  },
];
